<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Malenko</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Malenko</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why Not Records</title>
      <link>/posts/why-records-c-sharp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/why-records-c-sharp/</guid>
      <description>Glimpsing into the functional world from within the old world Why does this intrigue me and it should probably maybe spark something in you. Well C# has been around for ages, as F# and other functional languages and approaches. But it was never so much in demand as it is today. Or it might just be my current perspective and my exposure to my technical social circle. What this means, simplification of the way we present the world we see in our codebase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing the Decorator Pattern</title>
      <link>/posts/implementing-the-decorator-pattern-copy-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/implementing-the-decorator-pattern-copy-copy/</guid>
      <description>Already done and overdone. But never enough if you want to give it another try. Consider a useful pattern that has been out there for some time, and it dared to never show its true form to you. Well, this has happened and it is still happening. We see it all around. And these patterns can be tricky to understand, to implement, to decide when to be applied and when not to be applied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automating NuGet Version, Restore, Build, Pack and Upload</title>
      <link>/posts/automating-nuget-package-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/automating-nuget-package-creation/</guid>
      <description>Why would I go through this tedious process to create this small NuGet of maybe gold, maybe silver, maybe just some invaluable thing. Unless I try I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t know. And that&amp;rsquo;s how I start each time when I see I am repeating tasks.
As you type your day away, you turn around and see a small simple chunk of code that you think, hey, this guy here, he would be a handful in other places than just this lonely solution here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orchestrating a Fresh Environment Setup</title>
      <link>/posts/conduct-a-fresh-environment-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/conduct-a-fresh-environment-setup/</guid>
      <description>Orchestrating a Fresh Environment The following section will contain some ranting. Please feel free to skip at your own choice.
Why? Why not just install everything and be done with it. Just do whatever you want and need, set up your environment on a whim without any consequences. Well, that is a good question, and an answer would be that I decided to learn a new approach(or tool) that would help me in my everyday work life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
